<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jacob Zietek</title>
    <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jacob Zietek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recent Advancements in Language-Capable Robotics</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/ml_purdue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/ml_purdue/</guid>
      <description>Creating a club changed my life
Last updated 2023-08-29
Stop being weird, go talk to people. You&amp;rsquo;re not above people who have less technical knowledge than you, you just choose to spend more of your time in one thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Advancements in Language-Capable Robotics</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/recent-advancements-in-language-capable-robots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/recent-advancements-in-language-capable-robots/</guid>
      <description>The love child of Robotics and NLP.
Introduction Language-capable robots are the love child of exciting recent developments in Large Language Models (LLMs), Natural Language Processing (NLP), and robotics. This interdisciplinary field enables robots to interact with the world around them while understanding natural language prompts, opening exciting doors for robot-human interaction that was previously not possible.
Introduction to LLMs LLMs are deep learning algorithms that understand human-like language with a high degree of accuracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 14:09:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/photography/</guid>
      <description>Panasonic DMC-GX85
August 27, 2023
Panasonic DMC-GX85
1/20 sec | f/3.50 | 12.0 mm | ISO 400
June 29, 2023
Panasonic DMC-GX85
1/125 sec | f/5.60 | 150.0 mm | ISO 200
June 29, 2023
Panasonic DMC-GX85
1/200 sec | f/4.00 | 45.0 mm | ISO 200
June 24, 2023
Panasonic DMC-GX85
1/20 sec | f/5.60 | 150.0 mm | ISO 200
Rockefeller Center, 45, Rockefeller Plaza, Manhattan Community Board 5, Manhattan, New York County, City of New York, New York, 10111, United States</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 14:09:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/quotes/</guid>
      <description>Amor fati -Unknown
You&amp;rsquo;re not good enough yet, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more work to do. -Unknown
The things you think about determine the quality of your mind. Your soul takes on the color of your thoughts. -Marcus Aurelius
Gratitude gives you power over adversity. -Unknown
Comfort is the killer of man. -Unknown
You can lead a horse to water but you can&amp;rsquo;t make it drink. -Unknown
The world won&amp;rsquo;t lower its difficulty to cater to your weaknesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I cracked the coding interview.</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/cracking-interviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/cracking-interviews/</guid>
      <description>Technical interview questions are hard. It comes naturally to some&amp;ndash; I am not one of those people. In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll be going over some of the tips and tricks I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up over the last few years to improve in this domain.
Last updated Jun 14 2022 Technical interviews have become the norm for any company somewhat related to tech. With such a huge talent pool and limited spots at top companies, you&amp;rsquo;ll be answering at least one leetcode question to even be considered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I start working out?</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/how-do-i-start-working-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 14:09:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/how-do-i-start-working-out/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people have approached me since I started working out for advice on how to start out. This is both endearing and a little odd since I&amp;rsquo;m miles away from Arnold :muscle:. The demographic also tends to be people in STEM, so I&amp;rsquo;m glad we&amp;rsquo;re working on killing stereotypes. I still consider myself a beginner. Nonetheless, I wanted to record some of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve learned since starting my fitness journey and some of the common advice I dish out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
